Guide to the Big Band Arrangements Collection, 1990-2017 SC.2017.01
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Big Band Arrangements, I.
  - The Good Earth/Scoo Bee Doo (Woody Herman) (Box 12, Folder 722)
  - The Gypsy, Vocal (D) (Box 21, Folder 2199)
  - The House of Blue Lights (Box 24, Folder 2310)
  - The Hussle (Box 4, Folder 227)
  - The Lady is a Tramp, Vocal (G) (Box 11, Folder 693)
  - The Lady is a Tramp, Vocal (Box 14, Folder 895)
  - The Last Dance (Frank Sinatra) (Box 27, Folder 2496)
  - The Lemon Twist (Billy May) (Box 13, Folder 806)
  - The Man I Love (Ted Heath) (Box 27, Folder 2493)
  - The Meaning of the Blues (Stan Kenton) (Box 19, Folder 1173)
  - The Mole (Harry James) (Box 5, Folder 287)
  - The Moon is Blue (Stan Kenton) (Box 19, Folder 2025)
  - The New No Name Jive (Glenn Gray) (Box 21, Folder 2109)
  - The One I Love Belongs (Frank Sinatra), Vocal (F) (Box 20, Folder 2068)
  - The Party's Over (Stan Kenton) (Box 13, Folder 821)
  - The Preacher (Stan Kenton) (Box 12, Folder 725)
  - The Preacher (Woody Herman) (Box 28, Folder 2554)
  - The Queen's Aweigh (Bill Holman) (Box 2, Folder 81)
  - The Rotten Kid (Buddy Rich) (Box 15, Folder 944)
  - The Seasons (Autumn) (Bob Florence) (Box 30, Folder 3340)
  - The Seasons (Summer) (Bob Florence) (Box 30, Folder 3341)
  - The Seasons (Winter) (Bob Florence) (Box 30, Folder 3342)
  - The Serpent's Tooth (Miles Davis) (Box 15, Folder 940)
  - The Serpent's Tooth (Miles Davis) (Box 22, Folder 2219)
  - The Shadow of Your Smile, Vocal (Eb) (Box 20, Folder 2096)
  - The Shadow of Your Smile (Box 23, Folder 2279)
  - The Song is You (Bill Holman) (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - The Song is You (Frank Sinatra), Vocal (Bb) (Box 19, Folder 2023)
  - The Summer Wind, Vocal (C to Eb) (Box 28, Folder 2533)
  - The Sweetest Sounds (Charlie Barnet) (Box 24, Folder 2297)
  - The Thrill is Gone (Les Brown) (Box 3, Folder 156)
  - The Way We Were (Maynard Ferguson) (Box 17, Folder 1079)
  - The Way We Were (Box 29, Folder 2596)
  - The Way We Were (The Modernaires), Vocal Group (Box 17, Folder 1093)
  - The Way You Look Tonight (Stan Kenton) (Box 7, Folder 419)
  - The Way You Look Tonight (Box 8, Folder 471)
  - The Way You Look Tonight, Vocal (Eb) (Box 19, Folder 2008)
  - The Way You Look Tonight (Frank Sinatra), Vocal (Eb) (Box 20, Folder 2090)
  - Then I'll Be Happy (Count Basie) (Box 10, Folder 608)
  - Then I'll Be Happy (Tommy Dorsey) (Box 19, Folder 2032)
  - Then I'll Be Happy (Count Basie) (Box 6, Folder 323)
  - There Are Such Things (Tommy Dorsey) (Box 5, Folder 298)
  - There I've Said it Again, Vocal (Bb) (Box 11, Folder 652)
  - There I've Said it Again (Glenn Miller), Vocal Group (Box 23, Folder 2234)
  - There I've Said it Again (Glenn Miller), Vocal Group (F) (Box 7, Folder 431)
  - There I've Said it Again (The Modernaires), Vocal Group (Box 19, Folder 1192)
  - There Will Never Be Another You (Keely Smith), Vocal (Bb) (Box 25, Folder 2401)
  - There Will Never Be Another You, Vocal (Bb) (Box 27, Folder 2502)
  - These Foolish Things, Vocal (Box 14, Folder 899)
  - They Can't Take That Away, Vocal (Fb) (Box 12, Folder 756)
  - They Didn't Believe Me (Ted Heath) (Box 3, Folder 152)
  - They Say It's Wonderful, Vocal (F) (Box 20, Folder 2057)
  - Thing Called Love (Artie Shaw) (Box 24, Folder 2291)
  - Things We Did Last Summer (Stan Kenton) (Box 20, Folder 2067)
  - This is All I Ask, Vocal (Eb) (Box 9, Folder 553)
  - This Love of Mine (Count Basie) (Box 11, Folder 699)
  - This Love of Mine, Vocal (G) (Box 15, Folder 953)
  - This Love of Mine (Ray Anthony) (Box 20, Folder 2093)
  - This Love of Mine, Vocal (Ab) (Box 24, Folder 2328)
  - This Masquerade (Box 23, Folder 2276)
  - Thou Swell (Les Brown) (Box 6, Folder 341)
  - Three Blind Mice (Box 19, Folder 1168)
  - Three Feathers (Count Basie) (Box 10, Folder 612)
  - Three Little Words (Box 9, Folder 548)
  - Through the Eyes of Love, Vocal (Box 16, Folder 1025)
  - Tico, Tico (Box 23, Folder 2274)
  - Tico, Tico (Terry Gibbs) (Box 17, Folder 1060)
  - Tie a Yellow Ribbon (Les Elgart) (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - 'Till Then (Box 3, Folder 134)
  - 'Till There Was You, Vocal (G) (Box 12, Folder 728)
  - 'Till There Was You (Ray Anthony) (Box 25, Folder 2347)
  - Time After Time (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Time After Time (Stan Kenton) (Box 2, Folder 115)
  - Time After Time, Vocal (G to Gb) (Box 11, Folder 716)
  - Time Check (Buddy Rich) (Box 28, Folder 2568)
  - Time on My Hands, Vocal (G) (Box 28, Folder 2591)
  - Time Was, Vocal (Ab) (Box 28, Folder 2586)
  - Tinsel (Buddy Rich) (Box 28, Folder 2580)
  - Tip Toe Through the Tulips (Les Elgart) (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - To Each His Own (Box 24, Folder 2326)
  - Tomorrow's Blues Today (Count Basie) (Box 17, Folder 1037)
  - Too Close for Comfort (Ted Heath) (Box 11, Folder 684)
  - Too Close for Comfort (Harry James) (Box 23, Folder 2247)
  - Too Close for Comfort, Vocal (Bb) (Box 28, Folder 2542)
  - Too Little Time (Glenn Miller) (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Too marvelous for Words (Les Brown) (Box 4, Folder 208)
  - Toot, Toot, Tootsie (Woody Herman) (Box 18, Folder 1144)
  - Toot, Toot, Tootsie, Vocal (Ab) (Box 9, Folder 523)
  - Traces (Harry James) (Box 3, Folder 146)
  - Train to Stuttgart (Count Basie) (Box 17, Folder 1088)
  - True Blue Lou (Box 18, Folder 1100)
  - Trumpet Blues (Ray Anthony) (Box 13, Folder 781)
  - Trumpet Blues and Cantabile (Harry James) (Box 11, Folder 690)
  - Trumpet (Box 12, Folder 738)
  - Trumpetcology (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Trumpetcology (Box 28, Folder 2563)
  - Try a Little Tenderness, Vocal (Ab) (Box 8, Folder 470)
  - Tuxedo Junction (Stan Kenton) (Box 6, Folder 379)
  - Tuxedo Junction (Glenn Miller) (Box 24, Folder 2325)
  - Twilight Time (Les Brown) (Box 3, Folder 149)
  - Twinkle (Les Elgart) (Box 21, Folder 2123)
  - Two Franks (Count Basie) (Box 15, Folder 968)
  - Two o'Clock Jump (Harry James) (Box 11, Folder 706)
  - Two o'Clock Jump (Box 28, Folder 2536)
  - Ultra (Harry James) (Box 22, Folder 2191)
  - Ultra (Harry James) (Box 24, Folder 2290)
  - Undecided (Buddy Rich) (Box 17, Folder 1041)
  - Undecided, Vocal (Ab) (Box 21, Folder 2108)
  - Undecided (Bob Florence) (Box 25, Folder 2372)
  - Under a Blanket of Blue (Stan Kenton) (Box 14, Folder 863)
  - Under Paris Skies (Bob Florence) (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Under Paris Skies (Les Brown) (Box 19, Folder 2030)
  - Under the Willow Tree (Claude Thornhill) (Box 6, Folder 380)
  - Unforgettable (Nat Cole) (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Unforgettable (Nat Cole), Vocal (F) (Box 7, Folder 395)
  - Unforgettable (Box 19, Folder 2004)
  - Unforgettable (Nat Cole), Vocal Duet (Eb) (Box 20, Folder 2084)
  - Until the Real Thing Comes Along (Frank Sinatra), Vocal (Bb) (Box 21, Folder 2140)
  - Until the Real Thing Comes Along (Frank Sinatra), Vocal (Box 24, Folder 2301)
  - Up a Lazy River (Bobby Darin), Vocal (Box 29, Folder 3305)
  - Up Tight (Buddy Rich) (Box 16, Folder 996)
  - Up, Up, and Away (Glenn Miller) (Box 14, Folder 844)
  - Vilia (Glenn Miller) (Box 2, Folder 116)
  - Vine Street Rumble (Count Basie) (Box 21, Folder 2144)
  - Volare, Vocal (Ab) (Box 20, Folder 2058)
  - Volare (Glenn Miller) (Box 20, Folder 2047)
  - Volga Boatman (Box 3, Folder 144)
  - Wack, Wack (Buddy Rich) (Box 16, Folder 998)
  - Wagon Wheels (Frank Sinatra), Vocal (C) (Box 21, Folder 2149)
  - Wail Tail (Woody Herman) (Box 28, Folder 2595)
  - Wailing Boat (Maynard Ferguson) (Box 14, Folder 862)
  - Walk, Don't Run (Count Basie) (Box 24, Folder 2294)
  - Walk in the Black Forest (Quincy Jones) (Box 13, Folder 787)
  - Walkin' After Midnight, Vocal (C) (Box 29, Folder 2631)
  - Walkin' My Baby Back Home (Nat Cole), Vocal (Db) (Box 19, Folder 2028)
  - Walkin' Shoes (Stan Kenton) (Box 8, Folder 449)
  - Waltz for Debbie (Bill Evans) (Box 26, Folder 2449)
  - Warm Blue Stream (Harry James) (Box 6, Folder 329)
  - Warm Valley (Duke Ellington) (Box 6, Folder 326)
  - Watch What Happens (The Modernaires), Vocal Group (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Watch What Happens (Box 11, Folder 653)
  - Watch What Happens, Vocal Group (Box 26, Folder 2429)
  - Watermelon Man (Woody Herman) (Box 14, Folder 887)
  - Watermelon Man (Woody Herman) (Box 14, Folder 867)
  - Wave (Buddy Rich) (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - We'll Gather Lilacs (Ted Heath) (Box 3, Folder 176)
  - We've Only Just Begun (Box 17, Folder 1164)
  - We've Only Just Begun (Tommy Dorsey) (Box 19, Folder 1195)
  - Wee Small Hours (Box 24, Folder 2315)
  - Welcome to My World, Vocal (G) (Box 27, Folder 2522)
  - We'll Get It (Tommy Dorsey) (Box 21, Folder 2160)
  - West End Blues (Ray Anthony) (Box 18, Folder 1106)
  - West Side Story (Buddy Rich) (Box 5, Folder 288)
  - Wha' Happened (Count Basie) (Box 10, Folder 620)
  - Wham, Re Bop Boom Bam (Glenn Miller) (Box 5, Folder 262)
  - What a Difference a Day Made, Vocal (Eb) (Box 19, Folder 1177)
  - What a Wonderful World, Vocal (F) (Box 20, Folder 2073)
  - What are You Doing New Year's, Vocal (Box 19, Folder 2002)
  - What are You Doing the Rest of Your Life (Box 19, Folder 2001)
  - What Do You Do in the Infantry (Glenn Miller), Vocal (Box 19, Folder 2014)
  - What I Did for Love (Box 10, Folder 639)
  - What Kind of Fool Am I (Count Basie) (Box 5, Folder 260)
  - What Kind of Fool Am I, Vocal (C to Db) (Box 9, Folder 541)
  - What Now My Love, Vocal (F) (Box 8, Folder 455)
  - What's New, Vocal (G) (Box 14, Folder 877)
  - What's New, Vocal (G) (Box 29, Folder 2614)
  - What's New Pussy Cat (Quincy Jones) (Box 20, Folder 2036)
  - What's New (Stan Kenton) (Box 20, Folder 2097)
  - When I Fall in Love (Stan Kenton) (Box 15, Folder 939)
  - When I Fall in Love, Vocal (C) (Box 21, Folder 2131)
  - When I Fall in Love, Vocal (C) (Box 25, Folder 2389)
  - When I Grow too Old to Dream (Box 3, Folder 178)
  - When It Comes to Love, Vocal (A) (Box 28, Folder 2548)
  - When It Comes to Love, Vocal (A) (Box 29, Folder 2606)
  - When Sunny Gets Blue, Vocal (C) (Box 15, Folder 930)
  - When Sunny Gets Blue (Stan Kenton) (Box 16, Folder 1002)
  - When the Lights Go On Again (Vaughn Monroe) (Box 23, Folder 2277)
  - When the Saints (Box 13, Folder 816)
  - When You Wish Upon a Star (Harry James) (Box 3, Folder 160)
  - When You Wish Upon a Star (Glenn Miller), Vocal (Eb) (Box 13, Folder 810)
  - When You're Smiling, Vocal (G) (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - When You're Smiling (Woody Herman), Vocal (Ab) (Box 27, Folder 2468)
  - When You're Lover Has Gone (Billy May) (Box 15, Folder 937)
  - Where is the Love (Box 2, Folder 120)
  - Where or When (Glenn Miller) (Box 10, Folder 645)
  - Where or When (Frank Sinatra), Vocal (Eb) (Box 25, Folder 2385)
  - Whispering (Les Brown) (Box 26, Folder 2468)
  - Whispering (The Modernaires) (Glenn Miller), Vocal Group (Box 6, Folder 317)
  - White Cliffs of Dover (Glenn Miller) (Box 14, Folder 859)
  - Who (Box 24, Folder 2332)
  - Who Can I Turn To (Box 19, Folder 1190)
  - When I'm Feeling Kind of Blue (Jonny Hodge) (Box 28, Folder 2574)
  - Why Can't We Be Friends, Vocal (Bb) (Box 25, Folder 2399)
  - Why Do I Love You (Les Brown) (Box 6, Folder 354)
  - Why Don't You Do Right (Benny Goodman) (Box 9, Folder 587)
  - Why Try to Change Me Now (Quincy Jones) (Box 14, Folder 851)
  - Willow Crest (Bob Florence) (Box 30, Folder 3339)
  - Willow Weep for Me (Stan Kenton) (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Winchester Cathedral (Box 7, Folder 420)
  - Winter Wonderland (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Witchcraft, Vocal (F) (Box 7, Folder 430)
  - Witchcraft, Vocal (F) (Box 22, Folder 2212)
  - With a Song in My Heart (Harry James) (Box 23, Folder 2257)
  - Without a Song (Frank Sinatra), Vocal (Box 19, Folder 2012)
  - Without a Song (Count Basie) (Box 13, Folder 790)
  - Wonderland by Night (Box 9, Folder 515)
  - Woodchopper's Ball (Count Basie) (Box 12, Folder 758)
  - Woodchopper's Ball (Woody Herman) (Box 4, Folder 201)
  - Woody (Bob Florence) (Box 16, Folder 999)
  - Woody's Whistle (Woody Herman) (Box 29, Folder 2607)
  - World on a String (Stan Kenton), Vocal (C) (Box 22, Folder 2210)
  - Would He (Woody Herman) (Box 2, Folder 96)
  - Wrap Your Troubles in Dreams, Vocal (Eb to F) (Box 25, Folder 2373)
  - Wrap Your Troubles in Dreams, Vocal (F) (Box 25, Folder 2376)
  - Yellow Bird (Box 3, Folder 163)
  - Yesterdays (Box 8, Folder 474)
  - Yesterdays (Stan Kenton) (Box 19, Folder 1172)
  - YMCA (Box 10, Folder 635)
  - You and the Night and the Music (Ray Anthony) (Box 7, Folder 433)
  - You are the Sunshine of My Life (Box 18, Folder 1117)
  - You are the Sunshine of My Life (Frank Sinatra), Vocal (G) (Box 20, Folder 2040)
  - You Better Love Me (Keely Smith), Vocal (G) (Box 27, Folder 2509)
  - You Don't Know What Love Is (Bob Florence) (Box 2, Folder 93)
  - You Go to My Head (Box 3, Folder 190)
  - You Go to My Head (Stan Kenton) (Box 16, Folder 1020)
  - You Go to My Head (Bill Holman) (Box 22, Folder 2223)
  - You Go to My Head (Bill Holman) (Box 27, Folder 2527)
  - You Got Me Crying Again (Stan Kenton) (Box 14, Folder 902)
  - You Light Up My Life, Vocal (Bb) (Box 7, Folder 385)
  - You Light Up My Life (Box 11, Folder 712)
  - You Light Up My Life (The Modernaires), Vocal Group (Box 19, Folder 1191)
  - You Made Me Love You, Vocal (Ab) (Box 2, Folder 107)
  - You Made Me Love You, Vocal (F) (Box 25, Folder 2365)
  - You Made Me Love You (Harry James) (Box 29, Folder 3327)
  - You Made Me So Very Happy, Vocal (G) (Box 2, Folder 123)
  - You Made Me Feel So Young (The Four Freshmen), Vocal Group (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - You Made Me Feel So Young, Vocal Group (Box 26, Folder 2433)
  - You Made Me Feel So Young, Vocal (G) (Box 7, Folder 429)
  - You Stepped Out of a Dream (Les Brown) (Box 8, Folder 473)
  - You Stepped Out of a Dream (Glenn Miller), Vocal (Box 12, Folder 721)
  - You Stepped Out of a Dream (Ray Anthony) (Box 13, Folder 840)
  - You Took Advantage of Me (Box 20, Folder 2089)
  - You Took Advantage of Me, Vocal (G) (Box 25, Folder 2398)
  - You Took Advantage of Me, Vocal (G) (Box 29, Folder 2605)
  - You'll Never Find (Lou Rawls) (Box 12, Folder 739)
  - You'll Never Know, Vocal (Eb) (Box 9, Folder 540)
  - You're Driving Me Crazy (Billy May) (Box 6, Folder 371)
  - You're My Everything (Les Brown) (Box 16, Folder 1012)
  - You're the Cream in My Coffee (Les Brown) (Box 26, Folder 2424)
  - You're the Top (Les Brown) (Box 6, Folder 328)
  - You're Never Know, Vocal (Eb) (Box 8, Folder 478)
  - You're Never Know, Vocal (Eb) (Box 22, Folder 2198)
  - Young at Heart (Billy May), Vocal (Eb) (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - You're Nobody 'Til Somebody Loves You, Vocal (F to Ab) (Box 6, Folder 347)
  - You're Nobody 'Til Somebody Loves You (Steve Lawrence), Vocal (F) (Box 21, Folder 2137)
  - Yours, Vocal Duet (Box 8, Folder 506)
  - You've Changed, Vocal (Ab) (Box 27, Folder 2477)
  - Zigeuner (Artie Shaw) (Box 6, Folder 364)
  - Zip-A-De-Do-Dah (Les Brown) (Box 13, Folder 805)
  - Zoot Suit Riot, Vocal (C) (Box 22, Folder 2206)
- Nine-Man Arrangements, II.
  - 720 in the Books (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - 920 Special (Box 35, Folder 484)
  - A Beautiful Friendship, Vocal (Ab) (Box 31, Folder 83)
  - A Day in the Life of a Fool (Box 38, Folder 807)
  - A Foggy Day, Vocal (Bb to C to G) (Box 35, Folder 447)
  - A Hard Day's Night (The Beatles) (Box 39, Folder 880)
  - A Man Without Love (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - A Profound Gas (Box 38, Folder 829)
  - A Quiet Tear (Herb Alpert) (Box 38, Folder 795)
  - A Sunday Kind of Love (Box 35, Folder 497)
  - A Taste of Honey (Box 37, Folder 772)
  - A Time for Us (Box 33, Folder 308)
  - A Tree in a Meadow, Vocal (Ab) (Box 37, Folder 686)
  - A Warm Breeze (Count Basie) (Box 38, Folder 782)
  - A Woman in Love (Box 38, Folder 837)
  - Achy Breaky Heart (Box 32, Folder 161)
  - Adios (Box 32, Folder 122)
  - After the Lovin', Vocal (Ab) (Box 38, Folder 806)
  - After the Lovin', Vocal (G) (Box 33, Folder 323)
  - After the Lovin', Vocal (C) (Box 39, Folder 855)
  - After You've Gone (Box 32, Folder 198)
  - Ain't Misbehavin' (Box 31, Folder 85)
  - Ain't Misbehavin', Vocal (Ab) (Box 36, Folder 605)
  - Al Dila, Vocal (F) (Box 34, Folder 442)
  - Al Dila, Vocal (B) (Box 39, Folder 860)
  - Alexander's Ragtime Band (Box 34, Folder 428)
  - All I Ask of You, Vocal (Bb) (Box 37, Folder 688)
  - All of Me, Vocals (Bb, C, G) (Box 37, Folder 714)
  - All of Me, Vocal (Bb) (Box 38, Folder 849)
  - All the Things You Are, Vocal (F) (Box 35, Folder 522)
  - All the Way, Vocal (Eb) (Box 33, Folder 263)
  - Alley Cat (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Alligator, Vocal (Ab to E) (Box 39, Folder 871)
  - Am I Blue, Vocal (C) (Box 36, Folder 570)
  - Am I Blue, Vocal (Db) (Box 37, Folder 689)
  - Amapola (Box 38, Folder 778)
  - Amazing Grace (Box 36, Folder 571)
  - American Patrol (Glenn Miller) (Box 38, Folder 771)
  - Amor, Vocal (Ab) (Box 35, Folder 451)
  - And the Angels Sing (Herb Alpert) (Box 34, Folder 385)
  - Anema Me Core, Vocal (Eb) (Box 35, Folder 450)
  - Angel Eyes, Vocal (A minor) (Box 36, Folder 616)
  - Another Somebody Wrong Song (Box 37, Folder 711)
  - Another You (Box 32, Folder 114)
  - Another You, Vocal (Bb) (Box 37, Folder 649)
  - April in My Heart (George Shearing) (Box 34, Folder 407)
  - April in Paris (Count Basie) (Box 34, Folder 393)
  - Aquarius (Box 36, Folder 559)
  - Arrivederci Roma, Vocal (Eb) (Box 37, Folder 723)
  - Arthur's Theme (Box 38, Folder 783)
  - As Long As I Live (Count Basie) (Box 35, Folder 496)
  - As Time Goes By, Vocal (Ab) (Box 37, Folder 661)
  - Asi Asi (Box 33, Folder 327)
  - At Last, Vocal (F) (Box 37, Folder 651)
  - At Last (Glenn Miller), Vocal (F) (Box 32, Folder 130)
  - A-Train (Box 37, Folder 720)
  - Auld Lang Syne (Box 35, Folder 452)
  - Autumn in New York (Box 36, Folder 586)
  - Avalon (Box 34, Folder 355)
  - Baby Face (Sammy Kay), Vocal (C) (Box 31, Folder 68)
  - Baby It's Cold Outside, Vocal Duet (Db) (Box 36, Folder 627)
  - Baby Back Shuffle (Artie Shaw) (Box 37, Folder 722)
  - Bad Bad Leroy Brown (Box 31, Folder 29)
  - Ballin' the Jack (Box 36, Folder 572)
  - Bandstand Boogie (Les Elgart) (Box 32, Folder 172)
  - Basin Street Blues, Vocal (Bb) (Box 36, Folder 612)
  - Baubles, Bangles, and Beads (Box 37, Folder 744)
  - Be Happy (Box 34, Folder 375)
  - Beautiful Ohio (Box 39, Folder 989)
  - Beer Barrel Polka (Box 37, Folder 675)
  - Begin the Beguine (Box 32, Folder 123)
  - Begin the Beguine, Vocal (C) (Box 33, Folder 241)
  - Beginning to See the Light, Vocal (C) (Box 35, Folder 523)
  - Bei Mir Bist Du Schoen, Vocal (D minor) (Box 37, Folder 698)
  - Besame Mucho (Box 34, Folder 388)
  - Bewitched, Vocal (Ab) (Box 37, Folder 712)
  - Beyond the Sea (Box 37, Folder 736)
  - Bim Bam Boom (Box 32, Folder 164)
  - Birth of the Blues, (Vocal F) (Box 33, Folder 243)
  - Black Magic (Box 36, Folder 563)
  - Blue Bayou (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Blue Flame (Woody Herman) (Box 38, Folder 790)
  - Blue Heaven (Box 32, Folder 117)
  - Blue Lou (Box 32, Folder 148)
  - Blue Moon, Vocal (Eb) (Box 37, Folder 655)
  - Blue Suede Shoes (Box 32, Folder 183)
  - Blue Tango (Box 35, Folder 528)
  - Boogie Blues (Box 32, Folder 107)
  - Boogie Riff (Box 33, Folder 220)
  - Boogie Woogie (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Boogie Woogie (Harry Boles) (Box 32, Folder 195)
  - Born to Lose, Vocal (Bb) (Box 34, Folder 400)
  - Brazil (Box 38, Folder 840)
  - Broadway (Box 34, Folder 332)
  - Brooklyn Boogie (Box 39, Folder 876)
  - Brothers Go to Mothers (Woody Herman) (Box 35, Folder 540)
  - Brown Jug Little (Box 31, Folder 81)
  - Bugle Call Rag (Box 33, Folder 495)
  - Bunny Hop (Box 35, Folder 550)
  - But Beautiful (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - But Not For Me (Box 34, Folder 378)
  - By Heck (Tommy Dorsey) (Box 34, Folder 412)
  - Bye Bye Blackbird, Vocal Band (Box 35, Folder 456)
  - Bye Bye Blackbird (Box 33, Folder 260)
  - C Jam Blues (Box 36, Folder 560)
  - Cab Driver, Vocal (F) (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Cabaret (Box 34, Folder 420)
  - Cachita (Box 34, Folder 436)
  - California Girls (Box 34, Folder 436)
  - Call Me Irresponsible (Box 35, Folder 520)
  - Camel Hop (Box 38, Folder 810)
  - Can't Get Used to Losing You (Frank Sinatra) (Box 35, Folder 459)
  - Can't Help Lovin' that Man (Box 39, Folder 853)
  - Can't Take My Eyes Off of You (Box 33, Folder 310)
  - Can't We Be Friends, Vocal (Bb) (Box 36, Folder 645)
  - Can't You Feel the Love Tonight (Box 33, Folder 271)
  - Canadian Sunset (Box 32, Folder 90)
  - Candy, Vocal (F) (Box 37, Folder 680)
  - Candy (Sammy Kay), Vocal (Eb) (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Cast Your Fate to the Wind (Box 38, Folder 835)
  - Champagne Waltz (Box 31, Folder 47)
  - Chances Are (Box 38, Folder 792)
  - Changing Partners (Patty Page) (Box 35, Folder 490)
  - Chantilly Lace, Vocal (F) (Box 38, Folder 823)
  - Charleston (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Charmaine (Billy May) (Box 32, Folder 146)
  - Cheek to Cheek (Box 33, Folder 265)
  - Cheek to Cheek (Box 34, Folder 401)
  - Cheerful Little Earful (Box 33, Folder 403)
  - Cheers (Box 37, Folder 724)
  - Cherokee (Charlie Barnet) (Box 31, Folder 49)
  - Cherry (Harry James) (Box 33, Folder 257)
  - Cherry Pickers Polka (Box 36, Folder 629)
  - Cherry Pink (Box 33, Folder 214)
  - Chicago, Vocal (Bb to C) (Box 34, Folder 374)
  - Chicken Dance (Box 33, Folder 314)
  - Chinatown (Box 34, Folder 404)
  - Choo Choo (Box 33, Folder 307)
  - Choo Choo Ch'Boogie (Louis Jordan), Vocal (F) (Box 35, Folder 482)
  - Christmas Song, Vocal (Ab or Bb) (Box 36, Folder 638)
  - Christopher Columbus (Box 32, Folder 162)
  - Clarinet Polka (Box 34, Folder 480)
  - Close to You (Box 38, Folder 827)
  - Close to Your Eyes, Vocal (Bb) (Box 39, Folder 867)
  - Close to Your Eyes (Box 38, Folder 841)
  - Coffee Time (Box 34, Folder 394)
  - Cold, Cold Heart, Vocal (C) (Box 36, Folder 643)
  - Colonel Bogey (Box 33, Folder 328)
  - Come Dance with Me, Vocal (Db) (Box 34, Folder 406)
  - Come Fly With Me (Box 33, Folder 217)
  - Come Rain or Come Shine, Vocals (Bb, G) (Box 36, Folder 644)
  - Copacabana (Box 33, Folder 227)
  - Corner Pocket (Count Basie) (Box 31, Folder 26)
  - Could I Have This Dance, Vocal (C) (Box 35, Folder 489)
  - Craziest Dream (Box 37, Folder 718)
  - Craziest Dream, Vocal (C) (Box 38, Folder 757)
  - Crazy, Vocals (Bb, C, G, Ab) (Box 31, Folder 56)
  - Crazy Rhythm (Box 32, Folder 147)
  - Cry Me A River (Box 37, Folder 660)
  - Cupid (Box 33, Folder 226)
  - Cute (Neal Hefti) (Count Basie) (Box 37, Folder 705)
  - Daddy's Little Girl, Vocal (C) (Box 31, Folder 27)
  - Dancing in the Dark (Artie Shaw), Vocal (F) (Box 38, Folder 832)
  - Dancing in the Street, Vocal (G, E, or C) (Box 37, Folder 669)
  - Danke Schoen (Box 32, Folder 149)
  - Dansero (Box 35, Folder 498)
  - Darktown Strutter's Ball (Box 34, Folder 431)
  - Darktown Strutter's Ball, Vocal Band (Box 38, Folder 777)
  - Darn that Dream (Box 34, Folder 346)
  - Day by Day, Vocal (Eb) (Box 37, Folder 693)
  - Day by Day (Box 34, Folder 397)
  - Day by Day, Vocal (F or G) (Box 35, Folder 471)
  - Day by Day, Vocal (F) (Box 38, Folder 787)
  - Daybreak (Barry Manilow) (Box 37, Folder 746)
  - Days of Wine and Roses (Box 39, Folder 858)
  - Dear Heart (Box 39, Folder 887)
  - Deep Purple (Box 34, Folder 430)
  - Delilah (Tom Jones) (Box 38, Folder 819)
  - Delilah, Vocal (E) (Box 39, Folder 869)
  - Delta Dawn (Box 37, Folder 749)
  - Desafinado (Box 37, Folder 700)
  - Dinah (Box 34, Folder 382)
  - Disco Jockey Jump (Gene Krupa) (Box 31, Folder 43)
  - Do Nothing 'Till You Hear From Me (Box 36, Folder 590)
  - Dock of the Bay, Vocal (D) (Box 36, Folder 573)
  - Don't Be That Way (Benny Goodman) (Box 33, Folder 309)
  - Don't Blame Me (Box 33, Folder 245)
  - Don't Cry for Me Argentina, Vocal (C to Db) (Box 38, Folder 826)
  - Don't Get Around Much Anymore, Vocal (Ab) (Box 35, Folder 427)
  - Don't It Make My Brown Eyes Blue, Vocal (G) (Box 31, Folder 31)
  - Don't Take Your Love From Me (Box 37, Folder 671)
  - Doodlin' (Box 38, Folder 834)
  - Down South Camp Meeting (Box 38, Folder 839)
  - Dream (Box 36, Folder 562)